bnpparibasopen.org 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy | BNP Paribas Open

**General Privacy Information**

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of bnpparibasopen.com (the “Website”), we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This Privacy Policy discloses and explains the privacy practices for this Website, what Personal Information and other information is collected from and about you, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information. By visiting this Website, and/or using the services offered on or through this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. The services on this Website may change and expand, and this Privacy Policy may change accordingly, so check back occasionally. This Privacy Policy is part of the [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.bnpparibasopen.com/terms-and-conditions) which govern your use of this Website in general.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may provide, or that we may obtain, other than through this Website, such as by phone, through postal mail and through other live and print media. Also, this Privacy Policy only addresses the activities from our own servers. Other websites (including but not limited to those websites that may be linked to this Website) may have their own privacy policies and practices, which we do not control.

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE TALK TO YOUR PARENTS OR LEGAL GUARDIAN BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE OR PROVIDING YOUR NAME OR OTHER INFORMATION TO THE WEBSITE. YOU MUST NOT SUBMIT INFORMATION TO THIS WEBSITE WITHOUT YOUR PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN’S PERMISSION.

**Privacy Policy Purpose**

To make your visits to this Website and use of the services available as purposeful as possible, you may be asked for personal information and certain information may be collected from your computer when you visit us. “Personal information” includes, for example, your name; home and/or business address; email address; telephone number; credit card and other payment information; social security number or employer identification number; demographic information and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual.

We are committed to protecting the information we collect so this Website users can feel confident about using this Website to explore the range of information, promotions, services and products we offer. For this reason, we have implemented a security program that we reasonably believe will keep information that is stored in our systems protected from unauthorized access (see the **Security** section below for more information and security qualifications). This Website is hosted in a secure environment and the servers/systems are configured with data encryption, or scrambling, technologies, and industry-standard firewalls. To protect the security of your credit card information when purchasing tickets or merchandise and/or making hotel, restaurant, or other reservations, we employ the industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. we also encrypt your credit card number when we store your order and whenever we transfer that information to participating merchants. 

**Right to Opt In and Opt Out**

You may have the right to “opt in” and “opt out” of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on this Website, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to receive correspondence from us. You may opt out of any communication with us by clicking the opt-out link in our communications, or by sending an email to website@iwtg.net stating that you would like to be removed from a specific list, or all communications. However, please understand that you may still be contacted by us in connection with your client relationship or as follow up from an event, activity, or purchase.

**The Following Information is Collected by Us**

**1\. User-Provided Information**

We collect Personal Information from and about users of this Website, for example, through such users’ activities, transactions, surveys, and completion of online forms on this Website. Such information is collected, for example, when users register or subscribe for accounts or features on this Website, make online purchases, complete surveys, post to or comment on our blog that we may make available on or through this Website, submit a comment or question to us using a “contact us” or similar feature on this Website, send us an email, or in any other way submit Personal Information to us via this Website. You may be able to send information about this Website, products and services to your peers, contacts, friends, and family members through this Website by clicking on a “Tell A Friend” or similar button on this Website or in an email we have sent to you. In some cases (unless you simply forward our email on your own), you may provide the name and email address of your contact to us. That information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

**2\. Website Use Information**

We may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies track where you travel on this Website and what you look at and purchase. They may store your preferences, the information in your shopping cart, and/or your username and/or password. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of this Website to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on this Website. Most web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, this Website or certain areas or features of this Website.

We may use clear GIFs (pixel tags) or similar technologies, in this Website and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a web page or in an email or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a web page or message. A clear GIF may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information.

**3\. IP Address and Click-through Information**

Our servers collect data about your server’s Internet address automatically when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you’re on the Internet. When you request pages from this Website, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our servers may also record the referring page that linked you to us; the pages you visit on this Website; the website you visit after this Website; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Website or a referral site; and other web usage activity and data logged by our servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer this Website. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with your Personal Information. Any or all of these activities with regard to website usage information may be performed on our behalf by our service providers.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

We will use your Personal Information, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings. We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both personal information and website usage information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of emails, mailings, and the like, such as our e-newsletters), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the right to **Opt In and Opt Out** section above. We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, this Website and emails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate. In general, other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not share Personal Information with third parties.

**Children's Privacy & Parental Consent**

This Website is a general audience website. We do not knowingly collect information any personal information from children under the age of 13 on this Website. If in the future we collect personally identifiable information from children, we will do so in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C 6501, et. seq.). Please be aware that we did not design this Website for, and do not intend for it to be used by, nor should it be used by, anyone under the age of 13. We specifically request that persons under the age of 13 not use this Website or submit or post information to this Website. Should we inadvertently acquire Personal Information or other data from users under the age of 13, we will not knowingly provide this data to any third party for any purpose whatsoever, and any subsequent disclosure would be due to the fact the user under the age of 13 used this Website and submitted Personal Information without solicitation by or permission from us or through this Website. Since some of the interactive features and services offered on this Website cannot be accessed without providing Personal Information, we recommend that parents or legal guardians use the Website with your child if he or she is interest in participating in an interactive feature or service of the Website.    

**Service Providers**

We may use third-party partners to help operate this Website and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Website or for our business (such as website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).

**Aggregate Statistics**

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, this Website and emails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

**Legally Compelled Disclosures**

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of this Website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**Business Transfer**

In the event that Desert Champions LLC (the owner of this Website), or substantially all of its assets, is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, user information may be one of the transferred assets.

**Security**

While we will endeavor to protect the security and integrity of sensitive Personal Information provided to this Website, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. If you contact us by email or a “contact us” or similar feature on this Website, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit. Do not send sensitive information (such as payment card information, social security numbers, employer identification numbers, passwords, or pin numbers) to us via email or via a “contact us” or similar feature on this Website. We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email. You consent to our use of email as a means of such notification.

**Consent to Processing**

By providing Personal Information to this Website, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories.

**Third-Party “Linked-To” Websites**

When you are on this Website you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other websites, blogs, or other electronic media not operated by us. These sites may collect personal information about you. We do not control sites that are operated by these entities and is not responsible for the information practices of the other websites. The privacy policies of any linked websites are the sole responsibility of the other websites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this Website by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Website. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of this Website or sending you an email.

**California Privacy Rights**  

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, our customers who are California residents have the right to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us in the manner prescribed in the following section titled “Contact Us.”

**Hotels, Hotel Packages and Services**

Transactions relating to the purchase of hotel accommodations, hotel packages (that include both accommodations and tournament access), and services are subject also to the [Terms and Conditions for Hotels, Hotel Packages and Services](http://www.bnpparibasopen.com/hotel-package-terms-and-conditions).  

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policies and practices, you may contact us at:

Desert Champions LLC  
78-200 Miles Avenue  
Indian Wells, CA 92210  
Attention: Webmaster  
Facsimile: (760) 200-8441

_Last updated: 19 April 2016_

© 2016 Desert Champions LLC. All rights reserved.
